discoverdatascience.org 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy | DiscoverDataScience.org

_Last Updated: June 1, 2019_

[DiscoverDataScience.org](https://www.discoverdatascience.org/) takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it. By using our Site, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

## Key Terms Used in This Policy

“Personal Information” is information that specifically identifies you or that, when combined with other information, could be used to identify you, such as your name, location, IP address, e-mail address, telephone number, or prior educational background information (e.g., GPA range, name(s) of prior institution(s) attended, or prior degree(s) earned).

“Cookies” are unique identifiers usually in the form of small data files placed on your device that send certain information about your activity on the website or in an email communication back to us or the authorized third party that served the cookie.

## Personal Information We Collect From You

 _Information You Provide_

By default, _we do not collect any Personal Information from you_. If you reach out to us at one of the email addresses listed in the Site, you provide us with your name, email address, and any Personal Information contained in your message, but at no point will we request Personal Information from you directly.

 _Information Collected Automatically_

We use Cookies and similar technologies on the Site and in email communications to help us better understand your use of the Site and how we can improve. For example:

  * Based on your cookie settings, we track information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited, when they were visited, and which hyperlinks and other user interface controls were used;
  * We log the IP address, operating system, and browser software you used when accessing the Site, and we may be able to determine from an IP address your Internet Service Provider and the geographic location of your point of connectivity; and
  * We may track and collect information from emails that we send to you, for example whether you opened the email or clicked on any links from the email.

Certain parts of this Site may require cookies. You can adjust your settings to limit tracking or decline cookies, but as a result you may not be able to use certain features of this Site or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your device or browser settings for more information on how to delete or decline Cookies and control your tracking preferences. This Site does not respond to do not track signals from most browsers.

## How We Use Personal Information

We use Personal Information:

  * If you so request, to connect you with vendors who will provide you with information about their products and services.
  * To respond to your inquiries.
  * For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our Site, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns.

## How We Share Personal Information

We will not disclose any Personal Information submitted to us directly via email. Should we need to disclose Personal Information to a third party in order to resolve an issue, we will request explicit permission from you before doing so.

Our goal is to connect you with excellent educational institutions active in data science. When you click on a link to one of these institutions’ websites, it will be logged by our systems and those of the institution. Once on the institution’s website, you may be prompted to provide further Personal Information such as your age, date of birth, gender, occupation, and education level. In such cases, we are not responsible or liable for the use or disclosure of your Personal Information by that institution, as it will be subject to their own privacy policies. Please read their policies prior to submitting.

PLEASE NOTE THAT WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR THE ACTS AND/OR OMISSIONS OF THIRD-PARTY VENDORS.

Finally, we use service providers for web hosting, email hosting, Site analytics, and other internal business purposes. These service providers may receive access to Personal Information. However, we require such service providers to: (i) enter into contractual agreements to abide by this Privacy Policy and applicable law; (ii) handle Personal Information in a confidential manner and maintain adequate security; and (iii) use Personal Information only as needed to fulfill the relevant purpose(s).

## International Privacy Practices

The Site is primarily operated on servers located and operated within the United States. Accordingly, when you use the Site your Personal Information will be transferred to the United States, which may not provide the same level of protection for your Personal Information as the country in which you are located. We are committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the privacy and confidentiality of Personal Information when it is transferred. If you reside or are located within the EU and such transfers occur, we strive to take appropriate steps to provide the same level of protection for the processing carried out in any such countries as you would have within the EU to the extent feasible under applicable law.

Controlling Your Personal Information

If you would like us to correct or delete Personal Information, or have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the address below.

Banshee Media, LLC  
111 Kaider Road, Uniontown, PA 15401  

## Storage & Security

We utilize reasonable administrative, physical, and technical safeguards to protect the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of the information that we collect, receive, store, and transmits. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure; therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. While we work hard to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent “hackers” or other unauthorized persons from illegally accessing or obtaining information.

## Children

We do not knowingly collect, use, or share the personal information of children under age 13 and this Site is not directed to individuals under 13. If we are made aware that we have collected personal information from an individual under age 13 we will delete this information as soon as possible.

Sensitive Information

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., Social Security number, driver’s license number, credit card number (unless necessary to make a purchase), information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Site or otherwise to us.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice. When we do, we will post an updated version of the Privacy Policy and revise the “Last Updated” date at the top. By using this Site after any changes are made means you accept those changes and the revised Privacy Policy.
